allclients.com 2009-05-08

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy 

AllClients.com has a simple privacy policy.

We do not share your personal information, email address, or any of the information you enter into AllClients.com with any other organization or individual.

The only people that have access to your data besides yourself (and anyone you give your login information to), will be AllClients.com technical personnel and/or persons that perform services for AllClients.com in connection with our business. There may be a rare occasion where we, or our service providers, need to review your data strictly for technical support purposes. In all cases your personal information, including your data is strictly confidential and never used for any purpose, and never shared with outside third parties.

We do not provide any information about our subscribers, customers or affiliates to any third party, except of course in the unusual event should we be required to do so by law. 

We do use cookies, but we do not tie the cookie to any personal information that you provide to us. We do not collect or combine any information that you provide to us with any other demographic information from any other sources. We do not use third party tracking services such as DoubleClick.

**Policy Modifications**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 1, 2005. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time effective as of another date that will be posted here, so be sure to check back periodically. 

**Comments and Questions**

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may [click here](mailto:support@allclients.com) to contact us with our feedback form.
